const music = [
    {
        number: "1",
        question: "Which English Sir has had No. l’s in the 50’s, 60’s, 70’s, 80’s and 90’s?",
        answer: "sir cliff richard",
        hint: "Singer of song Devil Woman"
    },
    {
        number: "2",
        question: "Billy Corgan is the lead singer of which alternative rock band?",
        answer: "the smashing pumpkins",
        hint: "2007 album Zeitgeist"
    },
    {
        number: "3",
        question: "Who had a No.1 hit with Ice Ice Baby?",
        answer: "vanilla ice",
        hint: "Full name: Robert Matthew Van Winkle"
    },
    {
        number: "4",
        question: "Jimmy, Robert, John and John: can you identify this rock band from the first names of their original line-up?",
        answer: "led zeppelin",
        hint: "Songs: Stairway to Heaven"
    },
    {
        number: "5",
        question: "What is the middle name of Sir Paul McCartney?",
        answer: "Paul",
        hint: "James is his first name"
    },
    {
        number: "6",
        question: "How many members are there in pop group Little Mix?",
        answer: "4",
        hint: "Between 2 and 7"
    },
    {
        number: "7",
        question: "Which famous film star danced (and flew) in the video to Fatboy Slim’s 2001 track Weapon of choice?",
        answer: "christopher walken",
        hint: "Quoted to have said: Obviously an actor draws on his own experience."
    },
    {
        number: "8",
        question: "Which 1977 hit single by the Spanish vocal duo Baccara is the best-selling single of all-time by a female group?",
        answer: "yes sir, i can boogie",
        hint: "Released in 1977"
    },
    {
        number: "9",
        question: "In what year did Elvis Presley die? (a bonus point for the month)",
        answer: "1977",
        hint: "This year Jimmy Carter became the 39th President of the United States"
    },
    {
        number: "10",
        question: "In 1975 Bohemian Rhapsody was number one for nine weeks. It was finally knocked off the top slot by a song with a name that appears in the lyrics of Bohemian Rhapsody. Name the song and the band that ended Queen’s number one success.",
        answer: "mamma mia by abba",
        hint: "Released 1975"
    },
    {
        number: "11",
        question: "What was Britney Spears’ first single called?",
        answer: "baby one more time",
        hint: "Released 1998"
    },
    {
        number: "12",
        question: "Reginald Kenneth Dwight is better known by what name?",
        answer: "elton john",
        hint: "Middle name Hercules"
    },
    {
        number: "13",
        question: "What was the name of Amy Winehouse’s second and final studio album released in 2006 and reached number one in multiple countries across the globe?",
        answer: "back to black",
        hint: "Released: 2006"
    },
    {
        number: "14",
        question: "Which band had a huge international hit album in 2002 with the record “A Rush of Blood to the Head”?",
        answer: "coldplay",
        hint: "Lead singer Chris Martin"
    },
    {
        number: "15",
        question: "Knights in White Satin was a 1967 hit for which band?",
        answer: "the moody blues",
        hint: "From Birmingham"
    },
    {
        number: "16",
        question: "Which band sang The Final Countdown?",
        answer: "europe",
        hint: "This band is from Sweden"
    },
    {
        number: "17",
        question: "What was David Bowie’s real surname?",
        answer: "jones",
        hint: "His original name was David Robert J****"
    },
    {
        number: "18",
        question: "How many members are there in South Korean mega boyband BTS?",
        answer: "7",
        hint: "Between 5 and 9"
    },
    {
        number: "19",
        question: "Which talent show judge managed Westlife?",
        answer: "louis walsh",
        hint: "Born Kiltimagh, Ireland"
    },
    {
        number: "20",
        question: "Who sang the 1965 James Bond theme, Thunderball?",
        answer: "Tom Jones",
        hint: "Born Treforest, Pontypridd"
    }

];

export default music;